Can we um get your vantage point on on
what happened on those two
interceptions?
>> Yeah, great play great plays by them. uh
corner blitz and you know trying to
throw a hot reaction and guy jumps up
and catches it. Great play. Um next one
tip ball lands in the right in that
guy's hands. So
um
>> yeah, good plays by them.
>> Did you feel like you guys were kind of
playing the exact type of game you
wanted to play before those two? Like
exactly how you would have scripted it
out to go win?
>> Yeah, we were playing pretty good. We
were playing pretty good. Um, you know,
we got a we got a turnover in the red
zone.
Uh, we sputtered on a couple drives, but
for the most part, we were moving it
pretty good. Uh, we were in a good spot.
>> How dialed in was that first half,
especially on from a third down
perspective, and how did you walk out to
the field in the second half? What was
going through your mind?
>> Yeah, we were executing. We were
executing. O line was protecting. We
were making plays. Um, you know, we we
were doing a good job.
>> Is there anything you could have done
differently on that Denver?
>> Um,
could have thrown it higher, I guess,
but linebacker was running out there
underneath of it. So, if I threw it
higher, he might have gotten involved,
too. Um, not really. That was our
reaction to that.
>> Is this just kind of one of those games?
Does it feel like a playoff game where
the team that just was able to make a
couple of those plays going away? Did it
feel like that as you went down the
stretch?
>> Yeah, you know, it was playoff playoff
atmosphere.
We know what kind of game it was for us,
>> them too. And then
>> um yeah, it was just it was intense out
there. Guys are fighting their butts
off.
>> Bill show you anything different uh than
on than what you saw on film this week?
>> They always do do things a little
different against us. Um but that's what
we expected. They were mixing a lot of
things up. They started pressuring more
in the second half. I thought we handled
it well. Uh
yeah, we we kind of we knew what to
expect. We knew how they like to play us
from from past meetings and uh we had
the answers.
>> When you lobby hard for the team to
resign the team against addition to
Jamar this off season, you obviously
didn't get much opportunity to see how
it all looked. Is this like what you
envision the type of offense that you
guys could be and the type of outfit
that you would be to an opponent when
you guys are all clicking like you did
today?
>> Yeah, we know we know what we can be. We
know what we can do, you know, when we
execute. Um,
and we're able to execute today for the
most part and uh we just got to do more.
>> Going forward, Joe, last four games,
your mental outlook, how do you approach
the last four games?
>> Just go and play well. uh go out, have
fun, play football. That's what I love
to do. So, that's what I'm going to keep
doing. I'm going to keep doing it at a
high level.
>> Is it bittersweet to have play
atmosphere today, but knowing that, you
know, this might be the only shot you
get at the field of the season. Haven't
really got to feel that for the last
couple years. I mean, how kind of
frustrating bit does that make all of
this?
>> Yeah, obviously we're not where where we
want to be as, you know, a team or an
organization. four and nine is not not
good. Uh but you know, we got four games
to
go and show high level execution, high
level play, play playm.
Um I'm going to relish the the
opportunity to to go out and play play
with these guys and um continue to try
to put on a show for for everybody
watching. And I hope that uh that comes
across and I hope that uh
I know I'm going to continue to to work
hard to put myself in a good position to
make plays.
>> The hard thing, Joe, that you see what
it looks like and how the whole offense
is helping how effective you guys can be
that you just might be out of time now.
>> Yeah, I mean that's um that's how the
cookie crumbled this year. uh you know
obviously I would have loved to have
been out there more and and be able to
to make an impact but um that wasn't the
case and you know I fought my fought my
butt off to to get back to this spot and
to be able to be out there with
everybody and for our organization in
the city. So that's what I'm going to
continue to do. I uh I take it very
seriously. I I love what I do and I'm
going to continue to do it.
>> Can you describe some of the catches
that Higgins made today? What was your
some of your descriptions of your
relationship with him and how he's able
to just make spectacular plays like
that?
>> Yeah, he's great. T's great. Uh and both
of those guys, Jamar and Teen, know that
um teams are going to have different
plans to
take one of them away. And you know,
they did not want number one to to beat
him today. Uh and so when that happens,
then T's got to step up and make big
plays, which he did. Um
and some that we would have liked to
have back, too.
Mike G made a ton of plays today. We had
guys making plays all over the field and
>> [snorts]
>> uh you know, unfortunately, we just
weren't able to to pull it out.
>> What's it like playing a guy in in a
game with a guy like Josh? I mean, do
you feel like you have to feel like you
got to match him or what's what's that
like trying to trying to keep pace?
>> Yeah, we knew what kind of game it was
going to be. Uh, obviously he's a great
player and makes plays in all kinds of
situations and, you know, I think the
last play was the epitome of who he is
as a player. Um, you got to account for
for everything with him and, uh, he did
a great job today. over the next four
games. You said organizationally, not
one. What do you What would you hope to
see over the next four games to show you
that this thing came more than 26?
>> I don't know. We're just going to go out
and try to execute and play well and win
games. Um, you know, we'll look at all
the big picture stuff when it's all said
and done this year.
>> This is like a lot of games you guys
have been in, shootouts where you come,
you score a bunch of points and don't
get there. How do you handle mentally
being in so many of these where 34 isn't
enough?
>> Yeah, I mean, you know, that might have
I think I've matured this year and
uh gained some perspective on on
everything when I was out. And I'm just
grateful to to be out there and be able
to be a quarterback in the NFL and be
one of the best. you know, I'm I don't
take that for granted and I work really
hard to, like I said, put myself in a
position to to do that, just like
everybody else in there. So, that's what
I'm going to do. I'm I'm a I'm a player
and I'm going to go and try to play as
good as I can and see where we're at,
see where we're at.
>> The first touchdown to T that was uh Did
that even make that he made that catch?
>> No, I've seen him make that catch a
million times. Uh,
you know, that's one where you just put
some air on it and let T go and make a
play and that's that's what T does.
>> What does it say about T that, you know,
he really do everything he could to stay
in the game, really was adamant that he
wanted. What does that say about him?
>> Yeah, he's a tough guy. Um,
I think he's gotten tougher over the
years. You know, back in the day, he
would get hit and I'd hold my breath cuz
he would lay there for a second and then
he'd pop back up. I think everybody
remembers that. Um, now his popup game
is pretty good. So, that's good to see.
Doesn't doesn't scare me quite as much.
Uh, but he's as tough as they come and
he's going to continue to make big time
plays and big time spots. That's that's
who he is.
>> Does that mean a lot to you when guys
are tough like that
kind of, you know, mentality about them?
What's that say to you?
>> Yeah. Well, it gives me a lot of
confidence throwing them the ball in a
lot of different situations. you know,
there's I'm going to protect them with
the ball as good as much as I can, you
know, over the middle and in vulnerable
positions, but you know, sometimes in
big spots, you're going to have to fit a
ball in there where a receiver is going
to know that he's going to get hit. Uh,
and when you have guys like T and all of
our guys really, um, it gives you a lot
of confidence to try to fit fit that
ball in those windows because, um, they
can handle it. You talked about the
perspective being from being out and
maybe how that's helped shape how you
view this season. Is it a hard balance
between I believe on Thanksgiving you
said you get paid a lot of money to play
a kids game. You're out there playing in
the snow in a game against you know one
of the top quarterbacks. You're having
fun. You don't come out to win to enjoy
that moment while also knowing you're
not where you want to be. Is that a hard
balance to make sure that you, you know,
remember these moments, but it doesn't
overshadow how you feel about what you
guys have to do so that you're playing
in the playoffs?
>> Yeah, it, you know, it h that's that's
been a struggle for the last couple
years, but I've grown and and matured
and understood the position that,
you know, we find ourselves in. Uh, and
certainly the last 10 weeks,
uh, has has shown me a lot. Um,
like I said, I'm just happy to be out
there. Uh,
you know, we we want to
win games and be in the playoffs and and
do everything that, you know, we say
that we're capable of doing. Um, but,
you know, when I came back, I knew it
was going to be an uphill battle. Uh, we
were we were 3 and8 at that point.
That's certainly not a playoff caliber
position to be in. Um,
and you know, really, we're we're still
not out of it. We're going to be we're
going to be three games back. I don't
know who who won between the Ravens and
the Steelers. Um, does anybody have some
information for me who did?
>> Steelers won.
>> Steelers won. Uh, I think that makes it
a little tougher. That that probably
lowers our our chances even more. But,
you know, that's how the cookie
crumbles. I knew, like I said, I knew it
was going to be an uphill battle for us
when when I was coming back. And that's
not, you know, that wasn't really in my
thought process too much. Uh, I just
wanted to come back and put on a show
and play well in front of everybody.
>> Siki said you guys that that touchdown
to him
kind of came up practice a little bit,
right?
>> Yeah, it was uh
>> Yeah, that was a fun one. uh you know we
saw a look in practice and you know
talked about it after and
um was just like Mike if you get that
look go ahead and and do that. Um that's
what he did and it was exactly how it
played out in in practice you know
slightly different but u very similar so
to be able to execute that it was that
was fun. Thanks Josh.
>> Thanks Josh.